(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
1 2 3 Let’s go！ 戌神どこ見てもドグラマグラ
1 2 3 Let's go! Inugami, bizarre everywhere you look
コロり揚げるの かなりHot
Deep-fry 'em till they're quite hot
みんなで蹴っ飛ばせジゴロウさん
Everyone, kick 'em away, Jigorou-san
Hey！ 噛み付くグルーヴ ラクリモーサ
Hey! A biting groove, Lacrimosa
みんな まとめて どこまでも 溢れな
Everyone together, overflow everywhere
ほら Up ＆ Foot ゴーサイン 敬礼 Dogs ＆ People
Look, Up & Foot, go-sign, salute, Dogs & People
絶好調 良いね アワー・オブ・ザ・サン
In peak form, nice, hour of the sun
もう 準備済めば 轟く空から Oh, boss！
Once ready, from the roaring sky, Oh, boss!
一歳から九歳まで 登り降る 坂なら
From age one to nine, if it's a slope you climb
むじむじ君に 優しく舞い飛ばす
To Muji-muji-kun, gently dancing and flying away
熱中症入る ねんね ころね Oh Yeah！
Heatstroke sets in, sleep-sleep Korone, Oh Yeah!
Oh！ Get out of my way！ ハイ ハイ アオー！
Oh! Get out of my way! High high, awoo!
What's going on business？ Oh Yeah！
What's going on business? Oh Yeah!
Oh！ 知らせのパレード ハイ ハイ アオー！
Oh! The parade of news, high high, awoo!
お利口に分け隔て パウ パウ
Divide equally like a good kid, paw paw
ワン ワン ドド ド ワンダリング ママさん
Wan wan dodo do, wandering Mama-san
ワン ワン ドド ド 船越の膝枕
Wan wan dodo do, Funakoshi's knee pillow
コントロールなさらない ワンチャン 全て輝く
Don't control it, wan-chan, everything shines
もう 絶対 景色 レギュラー ちょっとからむ時期
Already, absolutely, regular scenery
汗かくせっかく延期計画天狗の伝言リラクゼーション
Sweating, postponement plan, relaxation
ファミの笛添え ペロペロ 比べる
With Fami's flute, licking and comparing
空想のガラス みんな 見守るの
Fantasy glass, everyone watches over
ずっと待ちなさい 走らない 逆らわずに 金歯
Wait forever, don't run, without resisting, gold teeth
いっちゃうね プリンバイバイバイ
Going now, pudding bye-bye-bye
微笑至短 目配り 脳のよいしょ
Short smile, watching carefully, brain's yoisho
一歳から三歳まで もらすよ だから
From age one to three, I'll leak, so...
ドキドキ君に 凪の様子飛ばす
To Doki-doki-kun, sending the calm state
熱中症舞い狂う ねんね ころね Oh Yeah！
Heatstroke dancing wildly, sleep-sleep Korone
Oh！ Get out of my way！ ハイ ハイ アオー！
Oh! Get out of my way! High high, awoo!
What's going on business？ Oh Yeah！
What's going on business? Oh Yeah!
Oh！ 知らせのパレード ハイ ハイ アオー！
Oh! The parade of news, high high, awoo!
お利口に分け隔て パウ パウ
Divide equally like a good kid, paw paw
ワン ワン ドド ド ワンダリング ママさん
Wan wan dodo do, wandering Mama-san
ワン ワン ドド ド 船越の膝枕
Wan wan dodo do, Funakoshi's knee pillow
コントロールなさらない ワンチャン 全て輝く
Don't control it, wan-chan, everything shines
もう 絶対 景色 レギュラー ちょっとからむ時期
Already, absolutely, regular scenery
Alright 鎖に繋がれるなんて真っ平御免 遊ぼうぜ
Alright, I'm done being chained, let's play
商売一発 どデカい怒濤 惜しみない万象 満ちちゃって
One-shot business, huge surge, full up
通りとどき 影も時々 湿布 総パァ ノリノリノリノリ
Passing shadows, high energy
一歳から三歳まで 準備 チョキ チョキ パッ
From age one to three, rock-paper-scissors-shoot
You can go Bye Bye Bye セブン チョキ チョキ パッ Oh Yeah！
You can go Bye Bye Bye, rock-paper-scissors
同情も 失敗した とど どき どき が Oh Yeah！
I failed, heart throbbing is Oh Yeah!
Clap your hands! Wash your hands! ノリ ノリ ノリ パウ パウ
Clap your hands! Wash your hands! Energy, paw paw
ワン ワン ドド ド ワンダリング ママさん
Wan wan dodo do, wandering Mama-san
ワン ワン ドド ド 船越の膝枕
Wan wan dodo do, Funakoshi's knee pillow
コントロールなさらない ワンチャン 全て輝く
Don't control it, wan-chan, everything shines
もう 絶対 景色 レギュラー ちょっとからむ時期
Already, absolutely, regular scenery
1 2 3 Let’s go！ 戌神どこ見てもドグラマグラ
1 2 3 Let's go! Inugami, bizarre everywhere
コロり揚げるの かなりHot
Deep-fry 'em till they're quite hot
みんなで蹴っ飛ばせジゴロウさん
Everyone, kick 'em away, Jigorou-san
Hey！ 噛み付くグルーヴ ラクリモーサ
Hey! A biting groove, Lacrimosa
みんな まとめて どこまでも 溢れな
Everyone together, overflow everywhere
ほら Up ＆ Foot ゴーサイン 敬礼 Dogs ＆ People
Up & Foot, go-sign, salute, Dogs & People
絶好調 良いね アワー・オブ・ザ・サン
In peak form, nice, hour of the sun
もう 準備済めば 轟く空から Oh, boss！
Once ready, from the roaring sky, Oh, boss!
一歳から九歳まで 登り降る 坂なら
From age one to nine, if it's a slope
むじむじ君に 優しく舞い飛ばす
To Muji-muji-kun, gently dancing away
熱中症入る ねんね ころね Oh Yeah！
Heatstroke sets in, sleep-sleep Korone
Oh！ Get out of my way！ ハイ ハイ アオー！
Oh! Get out of my way! High high, awoo!
What's going on business？ Oh Yeah！
What's going on business? Oh Yeah!
Oh！ 知らせのパレード ハイ ハイ アオー！
Oh! The parade of news, high high, awoo!
お利口に分け隔て パウ パウ
Divide equally like a good kid, paw paw
ワン ワン ドド ド ワンダリング ママさん
Wan wan dodo do, wandering Mama-san
ワン ワン ドド ド 船越の膝枕
Wan wan dodo do, Funakoshi's knee pillow
コントロールなさらない ワンチャン 全て輝く
Don't control it, wan-chan, everything shines
もう 絶対 景色 レギュラー ちょっとからむ時期
Already, absolutely, regular scenery
ワン ワン ドド ド ワンダリング ママさん
Wan wan dodo do, wandering Mama-san
ワン ワン ドド ド 船越の膝枕
Wan wan dodo do, Funakoshi's knee pillow
コントロールなさらない ワンチャン 全て輝く
Don't control it, wan-chan, everything shines
もう 絶対 景色 レギュラー ちょっとからむ時期
Already, absolutely, regular scenery
あれ？ あれ？ ころちゃん遅いな。 これどうしようかなこれ。
Huh? Huh? Korone-chan is late. What should I do?
あれ？ みんな始まってるこれ？ あ、やべえやべえ。 鐘すぐこれ。
Huh? Has it started already, everyone? Oh, crap. The bell is soon.
パラパラ上がってるよこれ。 これパラグアイか？ パラグアイか？
The comments are fluttering up. Is this Paraguay? Paraguay?
パラグアイ…それ！ …か、パラグアイ！
Paraguay... There! ...Is it Paraguay?!
いやパラグアイ出してる場合じゃねえ。 ど…ああ！ ああ！
No, this is no time to be showing Paraguay. Wh... Ah! Ah!
ああ、ごめんごめん。 ころちゃん！ やっと来てくれたよ。
Ah, sorry, sorry. Korone-chan! You're finally here.
お待たせだよ本当に。 待って待って、はあ…息、息…息整えてからね。
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting. Wait, let me catch my breath first.
いやころちゃん来なくてびっくりしちゃってさ。 本当に。
I was surprised you didn't show up, Korone-chan. Really.
チョコのコーナー始まっちゃうんじゃないかなと思って。 ど…あ、待ってね、待って。
I thought the chocolate corner was going to start. Wh... ah, wait, wait.
あ、よし。 あ、時間ですね。 あ、ね、息、息ね。 ぜえぜえぜえ。
Ah, okay. It's time. Right, my breath... *pant pant pant*
はあ…ちょっと、すごいね。 一回、一回止めようか？
Whew... man, that's intense. Should we stop for a second?
一回大丈夫？ 水、水持ってくる？ 大丈夫。 ふう…
Are you okay? Should I get some water? I'm okay. *Sigh*...
運動不足だね。 そうだね。 そうだね。 うん、大丈夫。
I'm out of shape. You're right. You're right. Yeah, I'm okay.
ということで、お待たせ。 いきなり、いきなり寝てやる…びっくりしちゃったよ。
Anyway, sorry for the wait. Falling asleep so suddenly... you surprised me.
そんなこと、ちょっとね、間がちょっと怖くて。 あ、そうだね、ごめんね。
Well, the silence was a bit scary. Ah, you're right, sorry.
ごめんね。 ちょっと遅くなったね。 いや、全然全然。 いいよ、ありがと。
Sorry. I was a bit late. No, not at all. It's fine, thanks.
じゃあ始めてもいいかい？ オッケー、始めましょう。 行くぞ！
So, shall we start? Okay, let's start. Here we go!
じゃあ早速、始めるよー！ おー！
Then let's get started right away! Yeah!
ハッチポッチステーション
Hatchpotch Station
ウーウーウーウー
Woo woo woo woo
何でもありの 楽しい駅
Anything goes at this fun station
楽しい仲間
Fun friends
めったに電車は来ないけど
The train rarely comes, though
さあおいで ジャーニー
Come on over, Journey
みんなで一緒に グッチ
Together with everyone, Gutch
楽しく遊ぼ ダイヤ
Let's have fun together, Diamond
ハッチポッチ パーティータイム
Hatchpotch party time
ハッチポッチステーション
Hatchpotch Station
ウーウーウーウー
Woo woo woo woo
ハッチポッチショップの ダイヤさん
Diamond-san of the Hatchpotch Shop
(ハイ！)
(Hi!)
キュートでワイルド たまには喧嘩もするけれど
Cute and wild, though we fight sometimes
本当は優しい (そう？)
Truly kind (Really?)
世界の恋人 (ん〜？)
The world's sweetheart (Hmm?)
ニコニコ元気に ハッチポッチ ファミリー
Always smiling and energetic, Hatchpotch Family
改札口の ジャーニー君
Journey-kun at the ticket gate
(ナニヨ！)
(What!)
せっかちどんかち たまには遅刻もするけれど
Hasty and clumsy, though he's late sometimes
本当は真面目な (そうそう)
Truly serious (Right)
お人よし (どっこいしょ)
Good-natured (Heave-ho)
ワイワイ楽しい ハッチポッチ ファミリー
Lively and fun, Hatchpotch Family
とってもおしゃれ エチケットじいさん
Very stylish, Etiquette Old Man
(エチケットやで)
(It's etiquette)
いつでも元気 説教どこでも始まるけれど
Always energetic, though he lectures anywhere
下から読んでも (なんやろ)
Read from the bottom (What is it?)
上から読んでも (はちさつは)
Read from the top (What is it?)
じいさん天才じい ハッチポッチ ファミリー
Old man is a genius, Hatchpotch Family
ハッチポッチ ハッチポッチ
Hatchpotch Hatchpotch
(ハッチポッチ)
(Hatchpotch)
ハッチポッチ ハッチポッチ
Hatchpotch Hatchpotch
(ハッチポッチ)
(Hatchpotch)
ハッチポッチ ハッチポッチ
Hatchpotch Hatchpotch
(ハッチポッチ)
(Hatchpotch)
ハー…
Haa...
ハ、ハ、ハ、ハ、ハッ
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
ハッチポッチステーション (ステーション)
Hatchpotch Station (Station)
ハッチポッチステーション
Hatchpotch Station
ウーウーウーウー
Woo woo woo woo
うすべったい トランクちゃん
Thin and flat, Trunk-chan
(ミラクルマジック)
(Miracle magic)
いつでもワンワン吠えてるけれど
Always barking "woof woof," but
みんなの気持ちは ちゃんとわかってる
She understands everyone's feelings
かわいい仲間 ハッチポッチ ファミリー
Cute friends, Hatchpotch Family
お調子ものの グッチさん
The frivolous Gutch-san
(よっ！)
(Yo!)
ギラギラスターを ロマンティックに夢見て
Dreaming romantically of being a glittering star
歌って踊れば 誰でも笑っちゃう
If he sings and dances, everyone starts laughing
みんな大好き ハッチポッチ ファミリー
Everyone's favorite, Hatchpotch Family
ハッチポッチステーション
Hatchpotch Station
バン！
Bang!
イェーイ！
Yay!
いいスタートが切れたんじゃないの？
We've made a great start, haven't we?
本当だよ、そうだよね本当に。ね。
Exactly, you're so right. Yeah.
あれ？
Huh?
いいスタートが切れたんじゃないの？
We've made a great start, haven't we?
いいスタート！いいスタート、それ！
Great start! A great start, there it is!
ぼーっとしてた。
I was spacing out.
ここ！いいスタート！
Right here! Great start!
すごいすごい！初めて見た！
Amazing, amazing! It's my first time seeing it!
ぼーっとしてたよ。さっきも、さっきも見た。
I was spacing out. I saw it before, I saw it before too.
いい曲聴いてたらぼーっとしちゃったよ、本当にね。
I was listening to a good song and just spaced out. Truly.
ありがとね。
Thank you.
いいよ、全然いいよ。うん。
It's fine, totally fine. Yeah.
ということでございまして。これ外すね。
And so... I'll take this off.
えっ、あ、それ偽物なの？それ。
Wait, oh, is that a fake?
偽物じゃない、これアンジェリーナ。
It's not a fake. This is Angelina.
あ、可愛いね。なんかちょっと似てるね、世界観が。
Ah, cute. It kind of looks like you, the worldview.
似てないよ！似てない！
It doesn't! It doesn't!
いやいやいや。ということで、ころちゃん。
No, no, no. Anyway, Koro-chan.
はい。
Yes.
初めましてだね、これね。
It's nice to meet you.
初めましてだよ。ゴー☆ジャスさんは…
Nice to meet you. Mr. Gorgeous is...
あ、ちょっと…なんかちょっと水臭いな。ゴー☆ジャスでいいよ。
Ah, wait... that's a bit formal. Just "Gorgeous" is fine.
え、ゴー☆ジャスでいいの？
Eh, is just "Gorgeous" okay?
いい全然。お前らはゴー☆ジャスさんってつけろよ！
It's fine, totally. But the rest of you better call me Mr. Gorgeous!
あ、ころだけ特別ね？
Ah, so it's special just for Koro?
そう。ころちゃん。
Exactly. Koro-chan.
あ、じゃあ、ゴー☆ジャスはさ、芸歴何年なの？
So Gorgeous, how many years have you been in show business?
芸歴ね、恥ずかしいんだけどね、25年やってるね。
My career... it's a bit embarrassing, but I've been at it for 25 years.
大先輩じゃないか！
Then you're a great senior!
でもずっと売れてないから、全然。まだ若手。
But I haven't sold well at all, really. I'm still a newcomer.
売れてるよ！
You have sold!
まだ若手で換算してほしい。ありがと。
I'd like to be counted as a rookie still. Thanks.
そうなんだ。じゃあころと一緒ってことでいい？
I see. So it's okay if I'm the same as you?
そう。ころちゃんも若手？
Right. Is Koro-chan also a rookie?
ころ、6年目だね。
Koro is in her 6th year.
6年目。あ、ちょうどいいぐらいだね、フレッシュなね。
6th year. Ah, just about right. Nice and fresh.
まだ中堅かな？
Maybe still mid-career?
まだ中堅。うん。
Still mid-career. Yeah.
じゃあ同じぐらいだね、この、VTuber界とお笑い界みたいなね？
Then we're about the same. In the VTuber world and the comedy world.
感じだね。うん。
Something like that. Yeah.
ということでございまして。あ、そう。知らない…やっぱり僕のこと知らない人いるから…
And so... ah, right. There might be people who don't know me...
一回本気の自己紹介やっちゃっていい？
Can I do a serious self-introduction once?
あ、そうだね。いいよ。
Ah, that's true. Go ahead.
一回行きますよ、じゃあ行きますよ、行きますよ。
Here I go, then. Ready? Here it comes.
ワン、ツー！君のハートに…
One, two! To your heart...
レボ☆リューション！どうも、宇宙海賊の…
REVO☆LUTION! Hello, I am the space pirate...
ゴー☆ジャスです、よろしくお願いします！
Gorgeous, nice to meet you!
はい。宇宙海賊なんだね、そうなんだ。
I see. So you're a space pirate.
そうなんだよ、言っとかないとちゃんと。
That's right. I have to say it properly.
あ、じゃあ宇宙に住んでるってこと？
Oh, so does that mean you live in space?
いや、目黒区に住んでるけど。
No, I live in Meguro Ward, though.
目黒区なんだ。言っていいの、それ？
In Meguro Ward? Are you allowed to say that?
もういい全然、うん。ちゃんと住民票出してるから。
It's fine, totally. I've already filed my residency card.
じゃあ、芸歴24年の、目黒区の、芸人さんね。
So you're a comedian with 24 years... 25 years experience living in Meguro.
まとめないで！それぐらいの人も結構目黒区住んでるからね！
Don't summarize it like that! Lots of people like that live in Meguro!
同じようなね、宇宙海賊ね。
Similar kinds of people... space pirates.
あ、ちょっと待って。えっとね、今日ハッシュタグがあってね。
Ah, wait a second. Um, we have a hashtag today.
ハッシュタグ？
Hashtag?
そう。「戌神ころね6周年」ってつけてみんな呟いてね。
Yes. Everyone, please tweet using #InugamiKorone6thAnniversary.
これだ、これ！
This is it, right here!
はい。
Yes.
出てるよ、そこね。ここ！ここ！ハッシュタグ！
It's appearing right there. Here! Here! Hashtag!
ハッシュタグ！ハッシュタグ、それ！それ！ここ！
Hashtag! Hashtag, there! There! Right here!
ハッシュタグ！
Hashtag!
ないんだね、そのなんか国名みたいな…
You don't have that "country name" gag today?
ないよ。ハッシュタグはない。そこぼやかしちゃうと…
I don't. No hashtag for that. If I blur that part...
ハッシュタグがみんな呟いてくれなくなっちゃうからね。
Then everyone will stop using the hashtag.
ないのもあるんだ、できないのもあるんだね。
So some things you just don't have, or can't do.
ないときはないからね。
When it's not there, it's just not there.
あ、そうなんだ。
Oh, I see.
しょうがないよね。うん。
Can't be helped. Yeah.
ちょっとね…なんかちょっと二人の距離を縮めたい、なんかね。
You know... I kind of want to close the distance between us.
あ、なんか縮めちゃう？
Oh, shall we close it up?
今更だけどさ、いつも見てるころちゃんと違う雰囲気なんだけどこれ。
It might be late to say this, but your vibe is different from the Koro-chan I usually see.
いつもの見た目知ってるの？
You know what I usually look like?
知ってるよ、ちゃんと。見てきたよちゃんと事前に。
I know, of course. I properly looked you up beforehand.
嘘。あんまり変わらないよでも。
Liar. But it doesn't really change much.
変わらないの？これ。変わらない変わらない。
It doesn't change? Well, maybe not.
変わらないっちゃ変わらないけどね。そうだよ。
It doesn't really change much, I guess. Right.
ちょっと小さくなったぐらいだよ。
I just got a little smaller.
ちょっと小さくなったんだね。原寸がちょっと分からないですけども。
So you got a bit smaller. I don't know your original size, though.
ちっちゃいといえばさ、ゴー☆ジャスはさ…
Speaking of small... Gorgeous, you know...
どんな子供だったの？
What kind of child were you?
あ、ゴー☆ジャス？
Oh, Gorgeous?
そう。
Yes.
ゴー☆ジャスはね、結構田舎の育ちなんでね。うん。
Gorgeous was raised in the countryside, you see.
目黒区じゃないんだ。
So not in Meguro Ward.
目黒区じゃないんだ。福島県いわき市。うん。
Not Meguro. Iwaki City, Fukushima Prefecture. Yeah.
あのね、もう全然普通に。元々こういう派手なことしようと思ってない子供だったからね。
You know, I was totally normal. I wasn't a kid who planned on doing flashy things.
普通に虫捕まえてたね、小学校の頃とかはね。
I was just normally catching bugs back in elementary school.
キモ。
Gross.
嘘だろ！虫キモ！？
No way! Bugs are gross!?
嘘だろおい！
Are you kidding me!?
え、どんな虫、どんな虫？
Wait, what kind of bugs, what kind?
トンボとかセミとかね。みんなそうでしょう？
Dragonflies, cicadas, and so on. Everyone did that, right?
今の子供たちは違うのかな？
Are kids different these days?
そう、虫取り少年はいるよね。
True, there are still bug-catching boys.
え、ころちゃん虫捕まえたことないの？
Wait, Koro-chan, have you never caught a bug?
いや、ころちゃんはね、小さい時はね、虫大丈夫だったん、セミも掴めたし。
Well, Koro-chan was fine with bugs when she was small, I could even catch cicadas.
大丈夫だったんだけど、やっぱさ…
I was fine with them, but you know...
大人になったらさ、虫キモってなったよね。
When you become an adult, you're like, "Bugs are gross."
まあそれはしょうがないね。
Well, that can't be helped.
え、そのさ、目の星はさ、いつからできたの？
Wait, that star on your eye... when did it appear?
これ？僕がね、あのね、田舎から上京する時にね…
This? It was when I was coming to Tokyo from the countryside...
「スーパーひたち」っていう常磐線乗ってる時にね…
When I was on the "Super Hitachi" on the Joban Line...
宇宙人に連れ去られちゃったの。
I was abducted by aliens.
へー。
Heh.
でそれで、あの宇宙人のね、色々な施しを受けて…
And then, after undergoing various treatments by the aliens...
宇宙海賊として覚醒したわけよ。
I awakened as a space pirate.
あー。
Ah.
そうなんだ
So that's how it is.
そうそう。色々あって、設定変わっちゃったんだよね。
Yeah, yeah. Lots of things happened and my setting changed.
そうなんだ。
I see.
25年もやってるとそうだろう？
When you've been doing this for 25 years, that happens, right?
そうそう。
True, true.
これで、本当に夜勤みたいになっちゃって... ギャーッ！
It's almost like a night shift now... Gyaaah!
痛いじゃん、根性焼きって事じゃん。
That hurts, you mean like a cigarette burn?
これ、今初めて言ったやつだから、Wikiとかに書かないで欲しいね。
I just came up with that, so please don't write it on the Wiki.
ということで、Wikipediaに書いてください！
With that said, please write it on Wikipedia!
書くんじゃないよ！
Don't write it!
そうなんですよ。
That's how it is.
ゴー☆ジャスのこと知ってた？
Did you know about Gorgeous?
え、知ってるよ。
Yeah, I know you.
何で見たことある？
Where have you seen me?
見た目のインパクトが凄いからさ、忘れられないよ君のこと。
Your look is so impactful, I could never forget you.
あら嬉しい。そうだよ、地球儀持ってるなーって。
Oh, I'm glad. Yeah, I always thought, 'He's holding a globe.'
いつも思ってた。それくらい？
I always thought that. That's all?
面白いなじゃないの？地理詳しいのかなって思ってた。
Not that I'm funny? I just thought you knew a lot about geography.
ちゃんと国を指差してるって。
Like, 'He's actually pointing at the countries.'
ちゃんと指してるよ！地理詳しいんだなーって。
I am pointing at them! I thought you were a geography expert.
全然「面白い」が出てこない！
The word 'funny' isn't coming out at all!
面白いよ！25年もやってると面白いから生き残ってるんだよ。
You are funny! You've survived for 25 years because you're funny.
ころちゃんがそう言うことによって、リスナーもゴー☆ジャスを見てくれるようになるから。
By you saying that, Korone-chan, the listeners will start to watch Gorgeous too.
みんな！目黒区の芸人さんをよろしく頼むよ。
Everyone! Please support the comedian from Meguro Ward.
目黒区の芸人さんじゃなくて、宇宙海賊のゴー☆ジャスね！
I'm not a Meguro comedian, I'm the Space Pirate Gorgeous!
よろしくお願いします。
Pleasure to be here.
この後も、みんなの懐かしい曲がたくさん出てくるから。
There will be many more nostalgic songs coming up.
楽しみにしててね。
Please look forward to it.
懐かしい曲があるぜりあ！
Nostalgic songs... are Algeria!
ここ、アルジェリア！
Here, Algeria!
凄ーい。
Amazing.
ネタ終わった？
Is the bit over?
いや、カット割りしてからのそれ何？
Wait, why did you say that after the camera cut?
終わった終わった。もういい？
It's over, it's over. Are we done?
大丈夫。コーヒーでも飲んどく？
I'm good. Want to drink some coffee?
じゃあ休憩がてら、テレビでも見よう。
Then, let's watch some TV while we take a break.
ポチっとな。
Click.
やっぱパ　やっぱパ　イーシャンテン
Yappapa, yappapa, one step away from ready
はしゃぐ恋は　池の恋
A frolicking love is a carp in a pond
やっぱパ　やっぱパ　イーシャンテン
Yappapa, yappapa, one step away from ready
胸のタイは　抱かれたい
The 'tie' in my heart wants to be held
わけもわからずに　らんま　らんまで　日が暮れる
Without knowing why, the sun sets in Ranma confusion
君と会ってから　らんま　らんまで
Since I met you, it's been Ranma, Ranma
なんのかんのと　すったもんだの世紀末
One thing or another, it's a hectic end of the century
なぜもっと静かに　「好きだよ」と言えないの？
Why can't you say 'I love you' more quietly?
張り合うと私も　じゃじゃ馬になっちゃう
If we compete, I'll become a shrew, too
ベルも鳴らさずに　そよ風の様に
Without even ringing the bell, like a breeze
胸のワンルーム　住みついた君なの
You've moved into the one-room of my heart
迷惑よ　だけど　今夜だけいいわ
It's a nuisance, but tonight only, it's fine
（明日はいいわ）
(Tomorrow is fine)
やっぱパ　やっぱパ　リャンシャンテン
Yappapa, yappapa, two steps away from ready
踊るキスは　海のキス
A dancing kiss is a sea kiss
やっぱパ　やっぱパ　リャンシャンテン
Yappapa, yappapa, two steps away from ready
恋の味は　隠し味
The taste of love is a secret ingredient
見つめられるたび　らんま　らんまで　目が回る
Every time you stare, my head spins in Ranma confusion
恋になりそうで　らんま　らんまで
It seems like love, Ranma, Ranma
タンマタンマで　そんなもんねとお友達
Wait a second, wait a second, we're just friends
迫力で口説かれ　星の街逃げ出した
Wooed with intensity, I fled into the city of stars
夢見てたデートが　マラソンになっちゃう
The date I dreamed of turns into a marathon
かゆいメルヘンも　乙女には媚薬
Even itchy fairy tales are an aphrodisiac for a maiden
君の優しさに　包まれてみたいの
I want to be wrapped in your kindness
冗談よ　だけど　ハートは透けちゃう
Just kidding, but my heart shows through
（いつかは透けちゃう）
(One day it will show through)
やっぱパ　やっぱパ　イーシャンテン
Yappapa, yappapa, one step away from ready
はしゃぐ恋は 池の鯉
A playful love is like a carp in a pond
ヤパパヤパパ イーシャンテン
Yapapa yapapa, iishanten
胸のタイは 抱かれたい
The sea bream in my heart wants to be held
見つめられるたび
Every time you stare at me
らんまらんまで 目が回る
Ranma ranma, my head is spinning
恋になりそうで
It feels like it's becoming love
らんまらんまで お友達
Ranma ranma, we're just friends
訳もわからずに
Without even knowing why
らんまらんまで 日が暮れる
Ranma ranma, the sun is setting
君と会ってから
Since I met you
らんまらんまで なんたらかんたら
Ranma ranma, and so on and so forth...
すったもんだの世紀末
All the fuss at the end of the century.
あれは誰だ 誰だ 誰だ
Who is that? Who is that? Who is that?
あれはデビル
That is Devil...
デビルマン デビルマン
Devilman! Devilman!
裏切り者の名を受けて
Bearing the name of a traitor
すべてを捨てて 戦う男
The man who threw everything away to fight
デビルアローは 超音波
Devil Arrow is ultrasonic
デビルイヤーは 地獄耳
Devil Ear is super hearing
デビルウィングは 空を飛び
Devil Wing is for flying through the sky
デビルビームは 熱光線
Devil Beam is a heat ray
悪魔の力 身につけた
He's gained the power of a demon
正義のヒーロー
A hero of justice
デビルマン デビルマン
Devilman! Devilman!
初めて知った 人の愛
For the first time he knew human love
その優しさに 目覚めた男
The man who awakened to that kindness
デビルチョップは パンチ力
Devil Chop is punching power
デビルキックは 破壊力
Devil Kick is destructive power
デビルアイなら 透視力
Devil Eye gives him X-ray vision
デビルカッターは 岩砕く
Devil Cutter can crush rocks
悪魔の力 身につけた
He's gained the power of a demon
正義のヒーロー
A hero of justice
デビルマン デビルマン
Devilman! Devilman!
あれは誰だ 誰だ 誰だ
Who is that? Who is that? Who is that?
あれはデビル
That is Devil...
デビルマン デビルマン
Devilman! Devilman!
裏切り者の名を受けて
Bearing the name of a traitor
すべてを捨てて 戦う男
The man who threw everything away to fight
デビルアローは 超音波
Devil Arrow is ultrasonic
デビルイヤーは 地獄耳
Devil Ear is super hearing
デビルウィングは 空を飛び
Devil Wing is for flying through the sky
デビルビームは 熱光線
Devil Beam is a heat ray
悪魔の力 身につけた
He's gained the power of a demon
正義のヒーロー
A hero of justice
デビルマン デビルマン
Devilman! Devilman!
やい！良かったね！
Yay! That was great!
良かった！やっぱね、ころさんはね、可愛いんだよ。
It was great! As I thought, Koro-san is cute.
顔もそうだけどね、動きも可愛いんだよ。
Her face, but her movements are cute too.
全部可愛いんだよ。ゴー☆ジャス、見てた？
Everything's cute. Gorgeous, were you watching?
見てた見てた、めちゃめちゃ自画自賛するね。
I was, I was. You're really praising yourself.
でしょー？
Right?
このね、可愛く踊れるように頑張ったんだ。
I worked hard so I could dance cutely.
そうだね、いいこと言うね。
True, you've got a point there.
あれ？
Huh?
ちょっと待って。
Wait a second.
何？
What?
ちょっと、今どういうこと？2人いない？今。
Wait, what's going on? Aren't there two of you?
そうだよ、ダブルころねだよ。
That's right, it's Double Korone.
え？
Eh?
パペットのころちゃんと、
The puppet Koro-chan and...
こっちのVのころちゃん、2人いない？
the V Koro-chan here, aren't there two?
これどういう状況？
What is this situation?
ダブルころねだよ。
It's Double Korone.
んんー！マルチバースの幕開けだ！
Mmm! It's the dawn of the multiverse!
これ、2人でこれ喋れるの？これ。
Wait, can the two of you talk together?
そうだよ。ねー、ころさん。ねー。
That's right. Right, Koro-san? Right.
喋ってる！
They're talking!
え、ちょっと待って。
Wait, hold on.
ちょっと2人して。
Both of you...
僕の手の上げ下げゲームちょっとやって。
Try my hand-raising game for a bit.
右手上げて
Raise your right hand.
はい
Yes.
右手下ろす
Lower your right hand.
はい
Yes.
左手上げないで
Don't raise your left hand.
え、はい
Eh, yes.
左手下ろす
Lower your left hand.
え、はい
Eh, yes.
ぐるっと回って、はいポーズ！
Spin around, and pose!
はい
Yes.
え、ちょっと違うポーズになってる
Wait, that's a different pose.
違うよ、これはだってこっちは棒がついてるからね
No, it's because this one has a rod attached.
可動域がね、難しいだよこれ
The range of motion is difficult.
うわあ、これどうす、これわかるでしょ。可動域の問題だよ
Wow, what's this? I get it. It's a range of motion issue.
可動域の問題あったんだね
So there was a range of motion issue.
そうだよ
That's right.
うわあすごいなころねは。でも2倍ころねを楽しめるってことでいいかな
Wow, amazing Korone. So we can enjoy twice the fun?
そうだよ
That's right.
そうしようね
Let's do that.
うん
Yeah.
そうだ！せっかくダブルころねもいることだしさ
I know! Since we have double Korone here...
スクショタイムにしない？
Why don't we do a screenshot time?
あら、いいこと言う！
Oh, you said a good thing!
パペころちゃんのいいこと言うじゃない
Pape-Koro-chan, you're saying something good.
でしょ！
Right?
いいこと言うよ
You're saying a good thing.
えー、ゴー☆ジャスも入ってよ
Eh, Gorgeous, you join in too.
えー、いいの？
Eh, is it okay?
うん、みんなで写真撮ろうよ
Yeah, let's take a picture with everyone.
撮ろう撮ろう
Let's take it.
それもつけるんだ
You're putting that on too.
それもつける。ちゃんと残るものだから
I'll put it on. It's something that remains.
あ、パペころも持ちたいそれ
Ah, Pape-Koro wants to hold that too.
これ持ちたいの？
You want to hold this?
ちょっと…ありがとうありがとうありがとう
Just... thank you, thank you, thank you.
じゃ一緒に持ってね
Then let's hold it together.
うん、OK。これでいいかな
Yeah, okay. Is this good?
はい、OK
Yes, okay.
じゃ撮ってもらおう
Then let's have them take it.
撮っていこうかな。よし、撮りましょうか
Shall we take it? Alright, let's take it.
いくよ、はいポーズ！
Here we go, pose!
パシャ！
Click!
うわああ！ちっちゃい海坊主だ！なんだこれ？何これ？
Whoa! It's a tiny Sea Monk! What is this? What is this?
あ、ごめんころねすきーが来ちゃったこれ
Ah, sorry, Koronesuki came.
あ、これゴー☆ジャスに紹介してなかったねこれ
Ah, I hadn't introduced him to Gorgeous.
これはうちの、あの視聴者っていうのかな？リスナーなんだけど
This is our... viewer, I guess? A listener.
うん、ごめん今日あのリスナーもいるんだよ
Yeah, sorry, the listener is here today too.
あ、リスナーも！
Ah, listener too!
そう、ゴー☆ジャスにね紹介しようと思って連れてきてたの忘れてたんだ
Right, I brought him to introduce to Gorgeous but forgot.
びっくりした海坊主が急にやってきたぞと思った
I was surprised, I thought a Sea Monk suddenly appeared.
海坊主じゃない、ころねすきーださ
Not a Sea Monk, it's a Koronesuki.
あ、ころねすきーほら挨拶して
Ah, Koronesuki, come on, say hello.
こんにちは
Hello.
全然そっぽ向いてるんだけど
He's looking completely the other way though.
うん、ちょっとあっちしか向けないんだよねこいつね
Yeah, he can only look that way, this guy.
そういう仕様なのね
That's his spec, I see.
え、ゴー☆ジャスじゃこの子も入れてスクショいい？
Hey, Gorgeous, can we take a screenshot with this kid too?
スクショ撮っちゃいましょう
Let's take a screenshot.
OK、じゃどういうポーズにしようかな
Okay, so what kind of pose should we do?
どこそこ？
Where's that?
これはあのここの会場
This is the venue here.
言えないけど、うん
I can't say, but yeah.
はいポーズ！
Pose!
パシャ！
Click!
OK、いいよ
Okay, good.
あとじゃもう一ポーズぐらい行っとく？
Shall we do one more pose?
もう一ポーズ行っとく？どこそこ？
One more pose? Where's that?
どこ行きたい？
Where do you want to go?
行きたい国言っと？
Tell me the country you want to go to.
えー、目黒区
Eh, Meguro Ward.
ちょっと同じポーズになる…同じポーズだこれ
Wait, it's going to be the same pose... it's the same pose.
いくよ、せーの、パシャ！
Here we go, one, two, click!
いいじゃん！これは記念になりましたね
Great! This became a nice souvenir.
いいねいいね
Yeah, nice, nice.
じゃころねすきー、もう言うことないかな？
Then Koronesuki, anything else to say?
え、ころねすきーに言うことある？ゴー☆ジャスは
Eh, Gorgeous, anything to say to Koronesuki?
わか…えー、ゴー☆ジャスも応援してね
I don't... ehh, please support Gorgeous too.
どう、ころねすきー？
What do you think, Koronesuki?
何も言わないわ！ころねすきーは何も言わないわ！
He says nothing! Koronesuki says nothing!
声誰も当ててないじゃないか
Nobody's voicing him, are they?
あ、パペころね、そろそろ次の曲に行かなきゃじゃない
Ah, Pape-Korone, we have to go to the next song soon.
あらすごい、パペころね
Oh wow, Pape-Korone.
本当だ
Truly.
ではでは、お次の曲は…ジャジャンジャジャンジャン！
Now then, the next song is... ta-da!
おお、何々？え？
Oh oh, what what? Eh?
あ、ゴー☆ジャスちょっと見ててよ
Ah, Gorgeous, watch this.
バイオリン、バイオリン、あっそれ！これバイオリン！
Violin, violin, yo-heave-ho! This is a violin!
うおー、確かにバイオリンだ！
Whoa, it certainly is a violin!
ということで、ミュージックスタート！
With that said, music start!
ハニホヘトイロハ
Do Re Mi Fa Sol La Ti
ハロイニトヘホニハクインテット
...Yugata Quintet...
ゆうがたクインテット
Yugata Quintet
ゆうやけそらがそまるとき
When the sunset sky starts to dye
きこえてくるよゆうがたクインテット
You can hear it, the Yugata Quintet
YOU GOTTA QUINTET
QUINTET QUINTET
そら元気も勇気もわいちゃうぞ
Energy and courage will well up
ラララ楽しくみんなでさわいじゃおう
La la la, let's all make a fun noise together
涙なんかはかわいちゃう
Tears will dry up
気がつきゃほら春の夢の中
Before you know it, you're in a spring dream
YOU GOTTA MUSIC
MUSIC MUSIC
YOU GOTTA QUINTET
メトロポリタン美術館
Metropolitan Museum
大理石の 台の上で
On a marble pedestal
大理石のうえで
On top of the marble
天使の像 ささやいた
A statue of an angel whispered
ささやいた
Whispered
夜になると ここは冷える
When night falls, it gets cold here
冷える
Gets cold
君の服を
Your clothes...
かしてくれる？
will you lend them to me?
タイムトラベルは 楽し
Traveling in time is fun
メトロポリタン ミュージアム
Metropolitan Museum
赤い靴下で よければ
If red socks are okay
かたっぽあげる
I'll give you one
エジプトでは ファラオ眠る
In Egypt, the Pharaoh sleeps
石のふとんに くるまって
Wrapped in a stone blanket
呼んでみても 五千年の
Even if you call, a five-thousand-year...
夢を今も 見続けてる
...dream, he's still seeing today.
タイムトラベルは 楽し
Traveling in time is fun
メトロポリタン ミュージアム
Metropolitan Museum
目覚まし時計 ここに
An alarm clock, right here...
かけておくから
...I'll leave it set.
バイオリンの ケース
A violin case,
トランペットの ケース
a trumpet case,
トランクがわりにして
using them as trunks,
出発だ！
it's time to set off!
タイムトラベルは 楽し
Traveling in time is fun
メトロポリタン ミュージアム
Metropolitan Museum
大好きな絵の中に
Into my favorite painting,
とじこめられた
I was locked away.
あたたたた。
Ow, ow, ow...
え？海？
Eh? The sea?
もしかして、さっきの絵の中に入っちゃったのかな？
Maybe I ended up inside that painting from before?
どうしよう。
What should I do?
おーい！ころさーん！
Oi! Korone-san!
え？
Eh?
おーい！すけだちー！
Oi! Help is here!
え、これ、ゲーマーズのみんなじゃないか。どうしたの？
Eh, isn't this the Gamers crew? What happened?
溺れてるじゃん、どうしたの？
You're drowning! What's wrong?
ちょっとバカンスに。
Just on a bit of a vacation...
漕げてない、漕げてない。バカンスできてないよ。
You're not rowing, you're not rowing. This is no vacation!
助けるよ、助けるよ。
I'll save you, I'll save you.
助けてー、助けてー。
Save us, save us!
よいしょ。 よいしょ。
Heave-ho. Heave-ho.
あー、助かったー。
Ah, we're saved.
よかったー。
Thank goodness.
ダメじゃん。
That's no good.
てか、バカンスって、ころね誘われてないけど、何で３人で行こうとしてんの？
Anyway, a vacation? Korone wasn't invited, so why are the three of you going?
おい。
Oi.
あ、まあまあ、でも、こうして合流できたからね。
Ah, well, well, but we were able to meet up like this.
そうそう。最終的にはよかったなって。
Right, right. It turned out well in the end.
あ、そっか。そっかそっか。
Ah, I see. I see, I see.
じゃあ、４人でバカンスに行こうか。
Then, shall the four of us go on vacation?
行っちゃおうか。イエーイ！レッツゴー！
Let's go! Yay! Let's go!
って、おい！
Wait, oi!
違うよ、違うよ。あれ、どうしたの？
It's not that, it's not that. Huh, what's wrong?
こんなね、呑気なこと言ってる場合じゃないんだよ、ころねたちね。
This isn't the time to be talking so carefree, you know.
絵の中に閉じ込められちゃったんだよ。
We've been trapped inside a painting!
えーっ！？
Ehhh!?
え、だよね。まあ、でも、大丈夫だと思うけどね。
Yeah, right? Well, but I think it'll be okay.
軽いな。
That's casual.
あのね、ウチが聞いた、あの、噂によると...
You know, according to a rumor I heard...
何か、この海のどこかに、願いを何でも叶えてくれる宝箱があるらしいよ。
Apparently, somewhere in this sea, there's a treasure chest that grants any wish.
えーっ！？願いが叶う、宝箱！？
Ehhh!? A treasure chest that grants wishes!?
まあ、ちょっとどこにあるか分からないけどね。
Well, I don't really know where it is, though.
宝箱の力で、元の世界に戻してもらえばいいんだよ。
We can just have it return us to our original world with the chest's power!
おおー、すごい！
Ooh, amazing!
じゃあ、みんなで宝箱を探そう！
Then, let's all look for the treasure chest!
おーっ！
Ohhh!
波をちゃぷちゃぷ ちゃぷちゃぷ かきわけて
Splashing, splashing, splashing through the waves
(ちゃぷ ちゃぷ ちゃぷ)
(Splash, splash, splash)
雲をすいすい すいすい 追い抜いて
Sailing smoothly, smoothly past the clouds
(すい すい すい)
(Smooth, smooth, smooth)
ひょうたん島は どこへ行く
Where is Hyoutan-jima going?
ぼくらを乗せて どこへ行く
Where is it taking us?
(うーうーうー)
(Ooh-ooh-ooh)
丸い地球の 水平線に
On the horizon of the round Earth
何かがきっと 待っている
Something is surely waiting
くるしいことも あるだろさ
There must be painful things
かなしいことも あるだろさ
There must be sad things
だけど ぼくらは くじけない
But we will not give up
泣くのは いやだ 笑っちゃお
I hate crying, so let's laugh
進め
Proceed
ひょっこりひょうたん島
Hyoutan-jima
Hyokkori Hyoutan-jima
わあー！
Whoa!
あれ？ あれ？ あれ？
Huh? What? Wait...
みんなー！
Hey, everyone!
なんか海じゃなくなってるー！
Wait, it's not the sea anymore!
凍っちゃったね！ あれ？
It's all frozen! Huh?
ここはどこだ？
Where are we?
おっ！ おおー！
Oh! Whoa!
ちょっと、スカートスカート！
Wait, my skirt, my skirt!
元に戻った！
We're back to normal!
元に戻ってるー！ 戻ったんじゃー！
We're really back! We're back to ourselves!
元に戻ったということで、ミオしゃ自己紹介お願いします。
Since we're back, Mio-sha, please introduce yourself.
えー？ 自己紹介から？
Eh? Starting with self-introductions?
うちうち、うちだよ！ 大神ミオだよ！
It's me, me, Ookami Mio here!
かわいいねー！
So cute!
ホロライブゲーマーズの大神ミオです。
I'm Ookami Mio from Hololive Gamers.
次はフブキ！
Next is Fubuki!
白上だよ！ こんこんこん！
It's Shirakami! Konkonkon!
かわいいだろー？
Cute, right?
かわいいー！ 続いて！
So cute! Next up!
はーい、もぐもぐおかゆ！
Hoi, Mogumogu Okayu!
ホロライブゲーマーズの猫又おかゆだよ。もぐもぐ...
I'm Nekomata Okayu from Hololive Gamers. Mogumogu...
かわいいねー！ みんなかわいいねー！
How cute! Everyone's so cute!
そういえば、ころね、6周年おめでとう！
By the way, Korone, happy 6th anniversary!
ありがとー！ ありがとうみんな！
Thank you! Thank you everyone!
あれ、なんかころねだけ変わってるね？
Wait, only Korone looks different?
さっきの姿と違くないか？
She looks different from before, doesn't she?
これ？ しょうがないよねもう色々。
This? Well, things happen.
いいじゃないですか細かいことは！
It's fine, don't worry about the small stuff!
大人の事情ね。 大人の事情があるんだよ。
Adult circumstances, I see. There are adult reasons.
これ皆さん、ホロライブのパペットゲットしてくれてるかな？
Anyway, did you guys get these HoloLive puppets?
UFOキャッチャーとかで取れてたみたいだね。
They were available in crane games and such.
かわいい、かわいいねー。
Cute, so cute.
どうだったみんな、パペットでやってもらったけどさ。
How was it having us use the puppets?
いや楽しかった！ すごい新鮮だったよね！
It was fun! Very fresh!
あんまりやんないからさ、みんな可愛かったよ！
We don't do this often, so you were all cute!
楽しかったよー！
It was fun!
でもなんか我々よりちょっと大きくなっててね。
But they were a bit bigger than us.
そう、でかかった。 パクパク動いてるし。
Yeah, they were huge. And their mouths moved.
いずれみんなもあの姿にならねーかなと思うんだけど。
I wonder if we'll all become like that eventually.
なりたいよー！ パペットゲーマーズになろうよ！
I want to! Let's become Puppet Gamers!
いいじゃんやろうよ！ やろうよ！
Nice, let's do it! Let's do it!
運営さんお願いします。 みんなあの姿にしてください！
Management, please make us all like this!
お願いします！ お願いします！
Please! Please!
あと何話そっかな？
What else should we talk about?
なに、なに？
What, what?
ころねは6周年で、なんか無いの？ 抱負とか。
Korone, it's your 6th anniversary. Any goals?
抱負？ 6年だよ、6年。
Goals? It's been 6 years, 6 years.
6周年ってやばいね。 やばいよ。
6 years is crazy. It really is.
1年生が6年生になるんだもんな。
A 1st grader would be a 6th grader by now.
中1が高3になるんだよみんな。 やばくない？
A middle schooler would be a high school senior!
60歳が66歳になるんだよ。 やばくない？
A 60-year-old would be 66! Isn't that wild?
わかるー！ わかるよー！
I get it! I totally get it!
抱負かー。 でもさ、結構デビュー時期近いじゃん。
Goals... but our debut dates were quite close.
ころねの数ヶ月後には7周年だが、私は。
Wait, a few months after Korone's 6th, it's my 7th!
そうだよね、フブちゃん！ 白上7周年だわ。
That's right, Fubuki-chan! You're at 7 years.
ゲーマーズはデビュー時期が飛び飛びの不思議なグループなんだよ。
Gamers is a mysterious group with scattered debut dates.
おかゆとは近いんだけど。 じゃあおかゆと抱負決めたい。
Mine is close to Okayu's. So let's decide on a goal with her.
そうだね。
True.
でもやっぱりゲーマーズは、すごいマイペースなのがいいじゃん。
But for Gamers, being so relaxed is our best trait.
そういうプレッシャーに負けずに...
Without giving in to that pressure...
いつも通りの活動を心がけるみたいな抱負でもいいんじゃん？
maybe our goal should be to just keep doing things as usual?
なるほどねー！ いただきました！
I see! That's it!
いただきましたよ！ いつも通り！
We've got it! Just as usual!
いつも通り、マイペース！ 毎年いつも通りってことじゃん！
Always relaxed! That means we stay the same every year!
何も変わらないゲーマーズってことじゃん。 ほら、ペラペラ。
Exactly, the unchanging Gamers. See? We're so thin.
やめな、ペラペラ。
Stop calling us 'thin'!
待って。 せっかくパペット持ってるから、即興劇やりたい。
Wait. Since we have these puppets, let's do an improv skit.
即興劇？ うまくできるかな？
Improv? Can we pull it off?
大丈夫！ 6周年だから言うこと聞いてよ。 ミオしゃからね。
It's fine! It's my 6th anniversary, so listen to me! Mio-sha first.
うちから？ ころねとミオのお土産劇場！
Me first? Korone and Mio's souvenir theater!
お腹空いた、ミオしゃ。
I'm hungry, Mio-sha.
おっ、ころね、お腹空いたの？
Oh, are you hungry, Ko-ne?
お腹空いちゃった。 何か作ってあげようか？
I'm starving. Shall I make you something?
いいなー！ 何がいいかな？
Ooh, that sounds good! What do you want?
お前がいい！
I want YOU!
あばばばばば！
Ababababa!
なん、なんか… 謎の力で…
What... by some mysterious power...
あ、うまかったうまかった
Ah, it was delicious, delicious.
吹っ飛ばされていった
I was blown away.
次はじゃあフブちゃん行こうか
Next, let's go with Fubu-chan.
え、この流れで？
Eh, in this flow?
うまかったうまかった。行っておいでよ！
It was delicious, delicious. Go on ahead!
じゃ、フブ… えと、フブキとコロネ劇場！イェーイ！
Well, Fubu... er, Fubuki and Korone Theater! Yay!
あ、コロネだ、コロネだ
Ah, it's Korone, it's Korone.
あ、フブちゃん、とっても美味しいレストランがあるんだけど一緒に行かない？
Ah, Fubu-chan, there's a very delicious restaurant, won't you go with me?
レストラン？え、コロネおすすめのレストランってこと？
Restaurant? Eh, you mean Korone's recommended restaurant?
そうだよ。え、行きたい行きたい！
That's right. Eh, I want to go, I want to go!
あ、ここだよここだよ
Ah, it's here, it's here.
お、素敵なレストランだね
Oh, it's a lovely restaurant.
ここのレストランはね、すごい特別な食材を使っているんだよ
This restaurant uses very special ingredients.
特別な食材？何何何？
Special ingredients? What what what?
お前だよ！
It's you!
えええ！フブにゃん！
Eeeh! Fubunyan!
あーやだー！
Ah, no way!
フブにゃん…
Fubunyan...
謎の力で…
By a mysterious power...
あ、うまかったうまかった
Ah, it was delicious, delicious.
はい、おかゆだよ次
Okay, Okayu is next.
え、この流れ僕も食べられちゃうじゃん
Eh, in this flow, I'll be eaten too.
そんなことないよ、おかゆは特別だよ
That's not true, Okayu is special.
本当に？
Really?
あ、じゃあおかゆとコロネ劇場！
Ah, then Okayu and Korone Theater!
オカコロ劇場だ！イェーイ！
OkaKoro Theater! Yay!
あ、おかゆ、海に行きたくないかい？
Ah, Okayu, don't you want to go to the sea?
海？
The sea?
まださ、海開きには早くない？
Isn't it still early for the sea opening?
いいよ時期の設定はどうでも
It's fine, the timing setting doesn't matter.
あ、そうなんだ
Ah, is that so.
海行くよ、海！
Let's go to the sea, the sea!
ほら、海、気持ち良さそうだよ、入っておいでよ
Look, the sea, it looks pleasant. Go on in.
うーん、まだ冷たいよ、入りたくないー
Hmm, it's still cold. I don't want to go in~
大丈夫だよ、行け行け行け行け！
It's okay. Go go go go!
はい、上がっておいで、上がっておいで
Okay, come up, come up.
あー、寒いよまだやっぱり
Ah, it's cold still after all.
え、なんで海に入れたと思う？
Eh, why do you think I put you in the sea?
なんで海に入れたの？
Why did you put me in the sea?
下味をつけるためだよ！あばばばばば！
To season you! Ababababa!
あーうまかったうまかった
Ah, it was delicious, delicious.
満足か、三人食べて
Are you satisfied, eating all three of us?
ほら満足か、これで
Look, are you satisfied now?
満足！
Satisfied!
ありがとう、みんな。じゃあねー
Thank you, everyone. See ya~
じゃあねじゃないだろ！
It's not 'see ya'!
友情にありがとう！
Thank you for the friendship!
え、まだ歌う曲あるでしょ！
Eh, you still have a song to sing, right!
あ、そうだった。準備して！はい
Ah, that's right. Get ready! Yes.
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー・ゴー 1997
Mach Go Go Go 1997
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
Mach Go Go Go Go
かぜもふるえるヘアピンカーブ
The wind and the shaking hairpin curve
こわいものかと ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
Afraid of anything? Go! Go! Go!
ホワイトボディ マッハ号
White body, Mach Go!
まけじだましい おやゆずり
A fighting spirit inherited from parents
はしりだしたら あとにはひけぬ
Once you start running, there's no turning back
ゆくぞしょうりのゴールまで
I'll go until the goal of victory
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー
Mach Go! Go!
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
Mach Go! Go! Go!
ちきゅうのはてまで アクセルふんで
Step on the accelerator to the ends of the earth
わかいいのちが ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
A young life is Go! Go! Go!
ナンバーファイブ マッハ号
Number 5, Mach Go!
みんなみてくれ そこから
Everyone, look at me from there
むねにでっかい ファイトがもえる
A big fight is burning in my chest
とばせせいぎの ハイウェイ
Speed down the highway of justice
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー
Mach Go! Go!
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
Mach Go! Go! Go!
うなるエンジン みなぎるとうし
Roaring engine, overflowing fighting spirit
まけてたまるか ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
I won't be defeated, Go! Go! Go!
スーパーバトル マッハ号
Super battle, Mach Go!
いくぞわがみち どこまでも
I'll go my own way, wherever it leads
シフトチェンジに ちからがこもる
Strength is put into the shift change
レッドゾーンで つきぬけろ
Break through in the red zone
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー
Mach Go! Go!
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
Mach Go! Go! Go!
Hey, you know what?
The rumor that you heard is true
"She's back in town"
Trouble "Wan"der!
Whenever, wherever
We're in trouble
She will come running, Run Run!
Trouble "Wan"der!
Up & Up & Down & Down & Left & Right & Left & Right &...
Um... let me see, what's next thing to do...
Doggy's back in town!
Sniff sniff... oh, find it!
Dig here, bow wow wow
Mmm... there's nothing here!!
Trouble "Wan"der!
Always spinnin' her wheels
You know, only working hard...
It's just the way she is
Trouble "Wan"der!
Up & Up & Down & Down & Left & Right & Left & Right &...
Let's take a break now, take a break now...
Doggy's back in town!
Back in, back in, back in, back in, back in town!
Doggy, Doggy's back in town!
Trouble "Wan"der!
Dokkin Dokkin Bakkun Bakkun
Heart pounding, chest thumping
Who can stop her?
Doggy, Doggy's back in town! Town! Town!
Doggy, Doggy's back in town! Town! Town! Bow wow wow!
Trouble "Wan"der!
Track down a suspect
Never get caught, alright?!
Doggy, do you hear me? (Wake up!)
Trouble "Wan"der!
Always doing her best
So she's lovable somehow
It's just the way she is
Trouble "Wan"der!
Yeah, it may be sometimes she's depressed
But never never shows that side
Cuz she's a really really wonderful wonderer
No no! She's a really Trouble "Wan"der!
Up & Up & Down & Down & Left & Right & Left & Right &...
Paw, Other Paw... Am I doing right?
Doggy's back in town!
Back in, back in, back in, back in, back in town!
Doggy, Doggy's back in town!
Trouble "Wan"der!
Dokkin Dokkin Bakkun Bakkun
Heart pounding, chest thumping
Who can stop her?
Doggy, Doggy's back in town! Town! Town!
Doggy, Doggy's back in town! Town! Town! Bow wow wow!
Trouble "Wan"der!
みんな、今日は見てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for watching today!
いつものころねもパペットのころねも可愛かったでしょ？
Both the usual Korone and the puppet Korone were cute, weren't they?
ということで、ここでグッズ紹介です！
And with that, it's time to introduce the merchandise!
戌神ころね活動6周年記念グッズが出ます！
Inugami Korone 6th Anniversary merchandise is coming out!
まず初めに、ころさんのパペットシアターB2タペストリー！
First up, Koro-san's Puppet Theater B2 Tapestry!
今回の配信に寄せて作ってもらいました。描き下ろしはフカヒレ先生です。いつもありがとうございます。
It was made especially for this stream. The illustration is by Fukahire-sensei. Thank you as always!
続いて、ころさんの耳カチューシャ！
Next, Koro-san's Ear Headband!
某遊園地で売ってる耳が好きなので作ってもらいました。
I love the headbands sold at a certain amusement park, so I had this made.
続いて、毛玉ころねクリップ付きぬいぐるみ！
Next, the Kedama Korone Plushie with clip!
これは肩につけることもできるので、お供にしてお出かけしてください。
You can attach this to your shoulder, so please take it with you on your outings.
続いて、こちら、ころねすきークリップ付きぬいぐるみ！
Next is this, the Koronesuki Plushie with clip!
欲しい人がいるか分からないけど、ころねが欲しいので作ってもらいました。これも、お出かけしてください。
I don't know if anyone wants it, but I wanted one, so I had it made. Please take this one out too.
全部買った方には、ステッカーと、ころねすきーへの感謝の言葉ボイスがつきますよ。
If you buy the full set, it comes with a sticker and a thank-you message voice for the Koronesukis.
発売は9時からとなっております。よろしくね！
Sales start from 9 PM. Don't miss out!
ゴージャス！ごめん、お待たせ！
Gorgeous! Sorry to keep you waiting!
いや、お待たせ。ごめんごめん。
No, I'm the one who kept you waiting. Sorry, sorry.
いやあ！いやあ！終わった終わった！
Wow! Wow! It's over, it's over!
終わった、お待たせね！
It's finished. Sorry for the wait!
いっぱいグッズ出すんだね！
You're releasing a lot of merch, huh!
うん、いっぱいそうだよ。いや、いいね！
Yeah, looks that way. Wow, that's great!
ドンドン儲かっちゃって！
You're raking in the cash!
そうだよ、お金ガッポガッポ！
That's right, the money's rolling in!
いやいやいや、すごいこと言うね！
Hey now, that's quite a thing to say!
やめてよ、そういうこと言ったら！
Stop it! Don't say things like that!
ごめんごめん、ごめんよ。
Sorry, sorry. My bad.
ゴージャスのさ、年収はいくらなの？つって。
So, Gorgeous, what's your annual income? I'm asking.
えっとね… 100万ギャラクシー。
Well, you see... it's 1 million Galaxies.
いくらかわかんないね。
I have no idea how much that is.
そう、そうしとこ。そうしとこ。
Yeah, let's just go with that. Let's go with that.
ゴージャスは今日どうだった？
Gorgeous, how was today for you?
いや、ちょっとね、ころちゃんと初めましてで、
Well, it was my first time meeting Koro-chan,
結構仲良くなれてね。そうだよね！
and we got along pretty well. Right!
ちょっとこれからなんかコラボとかもやっていけたらいいなと思ってる。
I'm hoping we can do some collaborations in the future.
いいじゃん！コラボレボリューションじゃん！
That sounds great! A collab-revolution!
コラボ、コラボ、レボ、コラボ、コラボ…
Collab, collab, revo, collab, collab...
いや、ちょっと、まだ合ってないね。
Wait, we're not quite in sync yet.
まだこれからだね。
It's still early days.
これから… 詰めていこう。うん。
From now on... let's work on it. Yeah.
何かゴージャスは何か言うことあったらいいよ。
If you have anything to say, Gorgeous, go ahead.
じゃあ、告知みたいな感じ？いいよ、いいよ、使って使って！
So, like an announcement? Sure, sure, go ahead and use the time!
えー、ゴージャス、2024年から…
Uh, Gorgeous, from 2024...
2025年にかけて、そろそろ…
through 2025, it's about time...
#戌神ころね6周年 3Dパペットライブ！？
#InugamiKorone6thAnniversary 3D Puppet Live!?
あ！オッケー！
Ah! Okay!
あ、神様が… もう終われって。
Ah, the gods are... telling us to end it.
神様がね、助かったーって思ってるところもある、ちょっと。
The gods, huh. Part of me is thinking, "Saved!"
あ、そうなの？そうなんだ。わかった。
Oh, really? Is that so. I see.
じゃあさ、見てる人たちにバイバイしようか。
Well then, shall we say goodbye to the viewers?
オッケー、バイバイしちゃおう。
Okay, let's say goodbye.
せーの！バイバーイ！
One, two... Bye-bye!
6周年
6th Anniversary
もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munch munch, munch munch
世界が終わる前に
Before the world ends
もぐもぐやみぃ マジ神
Mogu Mogu Yummy, truly god-tier
やむやむ ありのまんま
Yamu Yamu, just the way it is
もぐもぐやみぃ Magic Coming
Mogu Mogu Yummy, Magic Coming
この世を味わうんだ うまうま
I'm going to taste this world, delicious